I don't like a climber and I told Nick
my all this when he called into the show
I didn't appreciate how he treated my
friend and I'm not I'm not a fan a guy
I'm still a fan I still root for him I
still think he's hot I still would date
him I'd still all those things are still
in the air for me with Nick Viall
I'm open to redemption I'll never say
he's I think he's funny
I think he's fun to hang out with I had
a good time good conversations with him
I was very turned on by him and everyone
goes Nicky okay well picture yourself
dating Nick Viall what are you guys
gonna talk about what are you gonna like
are you really gonna enjoy this person's
company and my answer is yes I actually
even if I go blind
I think he'd still be fun today because
you can still feel it's like Braille
that says I'm very sexy
[Music]
Packt studio I'm so excited for all my
guest Sonya marina is here hi hi babe
Josh gondol man is here hello hello and
now from season 21 is that correct yeah
of the Bachelorette
No season 13 third season 13 of The
Bachelorette
originally from season 21 of The
Bachelor Rachel Lindsay is here and her
husband Brian Abbas Abbas Ola yep okay
I'm so sorry okay Abba solo you can
follow them at the Rach Lindsay and at
the Brian Abba solo on Instagram or on
Twitter the Rach Lindsay or the AB
doctor for Brian welcome to the show
thank you married when did you guys get
married August 24th yeah I was like I
don't care how you said his last name
she said husband you engaged for a while
like when you finally got married I was
like yes can't believe is still going
two years two years to 17 May 11th we
got engaged but we wanted to step away
from the spotlight and yeah get to know
each other in real life I mean you know
he's a chiropractor I was practicing at
the time so we just went back and kept
what kept us grounded and normal yeah
how long did it take to get back to like
normal when it felt normal
I think whenever you come off the show
yeah I'm the first really say six months
to a year roller coasters
oh yeah flying around and normal from
the jump I mean you know you do your
media tour after the finale they sit
they give you a ticket send you home and
they're like by SIA and then we're back
with family and they keep you grounded
more than anybody will check you did
they even though you're already engaged
were they like ticking clock when's the
wedding happening right away no we I
don't know if you tell a different story
but for me my parents they didn't get it
my mom I remember my mom was like I was
like I'm gonna take him to Houston to
meet grandma and the rest of the cousins
you know that couldn't be on TV and my
mom goes are the cameras coming no this
is the real thing
really engaged you guys we plan on
getting married so yeah it took some
time for our parents I think both our
families were on the same page when it
comes to let's have you guys get to know
each other yeah and so were you or were
you guys like we get it like this is
this actually worked and we know it
worked or were you a little bit like
maybe this was just a bubble that we
fell in love in and maybe it isn't gonna
pan out or did you trust it I think
we've met each other's expectations on
the show and then after the fact that
just got better and better so that was
our sign wild and if you want to watch
them fall in love you can watch their
season now for free on to be tu bi it's
a free streaming service and the season
of The Bachelorette win which Rachel and
Brian met each other and fell in love is
currently streaming or it will be
tomorrow on October 1st it's it was such
a good season thank you and um I was
dramatic for us because we weren't sure
how I was gonna go and then when when it
was revealed that it was Brian we were
just like oh yes because normally the
woman chooses the wrong way that we all
were hoping it would go you were so
Brian you were so loving and like you
just pursued her and you weren't there
was nothing bad about you and you were
so transparent with your affection I
don't know and your intentions so we
were like my sister and I watch and
Nicky and I watch all the time and we
were just like it's not gonna go our way
she's not gonna pick him cuz he's he's
so great you know and they she's gonna
pull it she's gonna pick a Jed agreed
agreed
you were so your season was so fun and
it's it's hard it's hard to beat that
season it's it's been a while since I've
been that into the show yeah it was so I
wanted to ask you what drew you to the
show why did you do the Bachelorette why
did you do that why did you sign up
Brian I mean let's start with Brian what
what led you to be booked on this show I
see I had no intention of going on the
show I was always a fan goes with
ex-girlfriend's old watch and I'd be the
guy making fun of these guys like oh god
this guy has no charm no game he should
go home like I was into it yeah
it's a great show and guys that are
resistant to it just check it out and
you'll get hooked hard eye contact
do you watch it have you ever watched
have watched it and I fully embrace the
compelling drama
I just am never home at night stand up
yes social experiment and women dating
you know how to act yeah in its people
that say it's fake sorry maybe some of
the situations that they're put in are
you know exaggerated and but the
feelings are real and that's why I love
the show it's so real and that's why I'm
always attracted to bachelor guys like
ex contestants I love them I'm always
like just waiting for them to slide into
my DMS you how far did you get on his
season 3 that was number 3 you were
never okay so do we need to share
stories off start a podcast with me
Rachel bang and I was so excited I
thought it was my make-a-wish happening
when he did you guys you guys could bang
and have a podcast you could be like the
Fleetwood Mac of that I was like
can we have sex and do about Gus and he
was like I don't think that that's a
good idea
it was so I was I've been rejected by
Nick but just said but that's just Nick
there are plenty of other ones out yes
but I think they wouldn't accept your
offer
thank you but that's my point is that
I'm a charge people go why would you go
for these guys these beautiful guys on
the show that are just like on this real
and I go because they open themselves up
in a way that I tend to do on stage
which is like I share everything and and
you have to be cool with these cameras
being you have to be really vulnerable
to be on the show and it's a retracted
trait yeah so what made you want to go
be vulnerable on this show Brian
honestly I think my vulnerability came
from being the oldest
my season you know 37 years old I had
dealt with all the BS you know my 20s in
the early thirties yeah I lived my life
I live my life so when I went on there I
knew exactly what I wanted and I let her
know night one like I want to know if
this if you're gonna be my person or if
not you know he said I mean I was
completely taken aback by him because he
was so forthcoming and he was so
vulnerable I was like there's got to be
something wrong with him but I mean he
was exactly who said he was if not even
better and for me it's so funny we had
completely opposite experiences I'm like
you I did not watch the show before I
wasn't into it it's time I think I'm
more of a housewife fan and we're not on
the show and by that I mean like people
of color so I was just like oh yeah I
know what that show is but we're not
represented well on that show it's not
my thing and then I got in this world
and I am hooked
I mean I'm believer it works for me to
change my life completely have you gone
back and watched seasons before you are
you going forward now what an incredible
answer my life goes forward there was
something about you being the oldest on
the season Brian that at the 37 at the
time which is like elderly for bachelor
contestant and but it just showed there
was a maturity there was a vulnerability
there was just a confidence that you
exude that made me go I want to see
older people in the show I even wrote to
Ilan when he was still working and I go
listen I'll be the Bachelorette I want
to be it so I'll go on I'll start out on
a season as a contestant but I am dying
to get on the show and he was just like
no Nicky we know if you were The
Bachelor you would reject all the guys
right away you'd be and I go you're just
saying I'm too I know you know I'm too
old I was 34 at the time I asked and
that is too old as a woman to be on that
show how old were you I was 31 you were
all this yeah I remember that yeah but I
want to see people that age looking for
love in their 30s because you know what
you want these 20 year olds I just I
just know even if they fall in love it's
probably gonna can't talk about that all
the time it's like imagine if
I look back in our 20s we were on this
show it's like we would have never
gotten together in your twenties you'll
break up with someone for again like a
bad haircut but it's it's true it's like
I I told them I go listen your demo is
aging I don't know if any of this is
true but I'm aging I don't want to see
20 year olds falling in love I just have
not invested in anymore I want to see
people that are actually worked on
themselves have some history and have
some depth get together it's so much
more interesting so if you're listening
ABC let's get some older people on the
show invite will very just mean 30s I
just want to do the show and I'm not
trying to plug but I am gonna plug but I
think that's what's great about going
back and watching past seasons on to be
because they have Trista and Ryan season
they have our season and so you may have
forgotten what it was like to see older
Bachelor people fall in love but it
works before all the social media and
all the new sense yep so to be is where
you can wait what watch a Rachel and
Brian's season and also yeah Tristan and
Ryan Ryan and Brian Huskey she's a
friend of mine yeah the Fisher the
official bachelor/bachelorette podcast I
love that you put that official ones out
there happy hour with Rachel and Ally so
check that out and yeah you so you don't
practice law anymore I don't I stepped
away from it it was a decision because
people were like why aren't you
practicing that's how that's what we
knew you for and I'm like I have other
aspirations as well I mean I come from a
sports background which is why I do
radio for ESPN and I have a football
show night game night yep yep ESPN okay
you do know how you say you're on
basically after all the games that's
right and just go to a.m. till 2 a.m.
and Brian your chiropractor and you also
have a book is that correct
am i reading the whole like health and
nutrition wellness platform oh my god
okay Wow so what am I doing wrong what
something that I can do incorporate into
my life every morning depends on your
goals what do you accomplish um I
recently stopped working out and it's
fantastic I gotta say I just haven't had
time to workout in weeks and I feel
great
I've never like you know I just don't
have that burden every day of like I
gotta go to the gym you know that burden
when you're going as Jim right like all
day it haunts you and then you only feel
good for the hours after it until you go
to sleep and so I just don't have that
burden but to be fair she's very
athletic she walks probably like an hour
and a half a day in New York City just
like ancillary movements and is doing
like planks when she's bored really
giving up I really have and I love it
and until I need to start again I'm just
gonna embrace do you work out Josh I I
have what's do I'm like trying to figure
out what to do because I'm like thinking
about my human body and like I guess I
should probably just try not to die and
I have like I have a day planner that
goes through 2020 I would love to
outlive that it's not like right stuff
on my calendar like I'll be dead by then
[Music]
take the dog to the dog dentist because
your last words like I don't care I'm
dead Brian I okay how did you did you
know did you see Rachel did you know
Rachel was gonna be the Bachelorette
when I initially first uh actually was
my friend that called me I was literally
yeah I was literally in my office
treating patients no idea about the
Bachelorette I mean I was too old I
thought it was too old to be honest
because I'd seen all the other season so
she calls me didn't answer she then you
thought you were too black
so yes I went to an interview in Fort
Lauderdale I skip the line is my friend
had a little hook up there and yeah next
thing I know I'm in LA and next thing I
know I'm coming out of the limo so how
do you prepare for that like what did
she pack like honestly I did like a
little shopping spree right before okay
yeah yeah you're about to be on TV I got
a couple suits because I dress in scrubs
time I was in scrubs five days a week so
I own like two suits and then like okay
I need to step up my game
sorry first moment hold that question
does that want to hear yours oh is it
cool to go back and watch your first
moment talking like when he gets out
what is what did you say yeah no I
honestly I actually spoke in Spanish
yeah all my friends were yeah I love
watching the first moment that we met I
do I'm so cheesy when it comes to the
producers later on really thick when I
got out of the limo the Spanish music
was playing in the background I thought
I actually killed it the first thing I
got the first impression rose and I was
we know we know and the stylists on the
show told me that he said after the
first night you're gonna pick five guys
and they're probably gonna be your top
five at the very end and it's true yep
yep you just know it's so but so your
first conversation that night what was
that use you were you laid it on you
really good I just told her I was very
direct I just told her hey listen what
did you know though like when did you
one that I know yeah yeah I would say
Geneva it's the second date it's crazy
how in this bubble everything is so
heightened yeah look at the first day
you're like oh it's all sunshine blue
skies it's all a beautiful things just
so excited to get to know this person
but by the second day you're asking
those hard-hitting questions and you
start to see the personality of the
person by the after the second dates I
knew exactly who those guys were yeah
you gotta think I was
eating breathing sleeping Rachel Lindsay
you know I don't think people understand
that on the show they're like how do you
fall in love so fast and it's like
you're in this bubble and no TVs no
radio no bones you got it you got to be
the Bachelorette you got to be on that
show are you kidding me I was on Dancing
with the Stars and I loved the idea of
being on a show that it all that matters
is the thing that you're doing and you
get lost in it and everyone with you is
in the same it's like you get to check
out of your life and just it's so good
it's so fun you'd be such a great that's
why I know I was energy I would be so
good but I'm too old I need to like
start my own and and do like an on
lifetime or something you know like for
older women I want to see like a
straight-up elder elderly they'd have to
tie it in like she's like I remember
when Hitler was a choose older
bachelorettes or bachelors because they
feel like we won't be as entertaining
but my goodness you would be so
entertaining yeah it's I told Ellen I
was like I'd be getting fingered in hot
tubs I give you I I think I would I
would do everything yes exactly I would
be so interesting I promise you good
television but that you know they wants
it's a different show now it's like
turned into you know it's just watching
22 year olds think that they want to I
just don't believe a 22 year old knows
what they want I wonder if you could
hang like long term with it or if you'd
just be like I know this guy's not it I
can't make it to the rose ceremony I
just want to get rid of him that
couldn't fake it you mean yeah yeah cuz
I hear that you and I'm not gonna ask
you but I hear you have to cut you know
who you're gonna pick and you might have
to be like like kind of fake liking
others just to play the game and Elin
said that amigos you're not gonna be
able to like you'll know who you want or
you won't want anyone I go out you're a
professional actor I could do it I will
do every I'll do anything you guys want
me to do let me on what were you gonna
ask before just say I heard that you
have to bring
all of your own wardrobe to the show is
that really true oh my god I remember
this one guy he actually ended up crying
you know how the the first night ends
it's actually in the morning the Sun's
up already guy was crying he had bought
like a whole new wardrobe and went home
night one no he even said he's like I'm
Isaac I was gonna be the best looking
guy in that best-looking best dressed
guy in the house guess what really bring
evening gowns and like a stylist write
the lead gets the stylist but the
contestants they don't it's some of
these people quit their jobs to come on
this show they break the bank these
girls and especially the women like
really spend so much money and so much
like you're they're doing their own hair
and makeup I that was the thing I was
fascinated by I remember one time they
went to like New Mexico for one of the
things or Santa Fe and they all had like
turquoise jewelry and I was like where
did this shows up do they have a
turquoise like promotional thing and no
these girls just bought Santa Fe outfits
I that was the thing I would be
overwhelmed by it I need to be the
Bachelorette so that I have stylists
because I couldn't be two over one it's
like a sorority though I mean I walked
it and I didn't have the makeup I I mean
I was as far as gowns were concerned I
went to like a local boutique in Dallas
was like hey I'm about to be on the show
I can't tell you what it is but it's a
it's a big-time show and your dresses
will be featured every week and they
make sure and they gave me eight dresses
but then you have girls who are doing
your makeup who are giving you skin care
tips I mean it's really a fun situation
Oh like your housemates
yeah trade clothes I mean at the wedding
we had guys from my season that are his
friends yeah girls that were on Knicks
season with me yeah it would've been a
great place for you to meet some of the
guys I think guys want to go to one of
these weddings my aunt's were hitting on
the men I tell you I just want to start
a podcast
yeah I guess Ashley and Jared just got
married and I was asking someone about
their like who's hooking up that like it
was okay I saw Kaitlyn Bristowe and she
was talking about it I'm like I'm dying
to get an invite to one of these
weddings
that's where yeah that's where the
hookups happen that you find out about
later on bachelor in paradise or Knicks
season remember God and you never did a
bachelor in paradise no no thank God I
didn't I don't think I would survive
that Ali and I talk about that all the
time on the podcast right thank goodness
we really spared a bachelor in paradise
that wouldn't have worked that method is
not good for me yeah what do you mean by
that like you think I meet Brian Brian
comes down and we hit it off and then
this other girl comes walking down the
beach yeah and then he goes on the date
oh I wouldn't be there when he got back
I think I'm just too jealous it's like
if you know you know you should be here
for me I wouldn't know actually probably
with some kind of it so it's such it's
such great TV again you can catch out
you can catch Rachel's season where she
meets her husband Brian on The
Bachelorette
it is now streaming on to be and yeah I
just I have so many other questions when
you were on Nick's season and living
with all those girls I mean what was the
you said it was fun sorority like but
like it had to have been rough to like
see girls go out on dates with a guy
that like how are you you all like the
same guy that's so weird you're like
Mormon wives
we had a weird dynamic in the house like
my girls were cool so we didn't get
caught up in the drama of things that
Corinne was on my season oh right yeah I
loved Korean I still do it so keep in
contact yeah I do
she was invited to the wedding and
everything yeah and so we we just had
fun it's kind of like we know what we
signed up for it is what it is and also
you know who the guy is really into like
men do a terrible job at hiding their
feelings like we knew from the job we
were like he's gonna choose this Vanessa
girl
with the wrong head we were attracted to
Nick but we you could feel who he was
gonna pick so at that point we were just
like you know what we're just gonna make
the best of it and have a really really
good time yes and we did that so yeah
you had a lot of fun in them yeah like
some crazy girls like is it just just
you drinking and partying and just
hanging out talking about boy yes I was
gonna say boys but boy that's
interesting that you knew sorry God no
no I was gonna say like the drinking and
everything we now they are limited on
their drinking so what I think I was the
last instance where you could just so it
was a Wilder time back that's so because
everyone's always drinking champagne and
there has to be they just don't show it
there was a girl on my season who didn't
drink at all
yeah Taylor she was completely so not
drink at all and so she would sleep that
is what my English Fox yeah I just so
that is interesting to me though that
you guys were like oh we know who he's
gonna pick let's just have some fun like
you knew you you do I don't know if if
you felt the same way on you know were
you like I'm gonna win this thing did
you know I was really confident two
months and you were just like the whole
time were you steadily like I think
we're really vibing here or where their
points were you're like oh there was
right before the the last date before
the proposal like I was really like you
know I just don't know what I'm gonna do
I just I'm just really conflicted yes
you you know you know come on at the end
you know if she walked in my room that
was down to me and the second person and
you know she was I knew she was a little
off because she was telling me like oh I
don't know it's Alden decisive in the
prior date she was so sure about things
she's just trying to throw me off so I
was I was completely confident though
but I would say the last day before God
I'm losing her testing it ow
I was always testing Brian because I
remember the first sign I thought he's
either gonna be my best friend or he's
gonna be my fiance at the end of this I
could just tell from the way we vibe or
both but it's not that you're conflicted
towards the end cause like you said you
know it's more of you're conflicted
about hurting people at the end of all
of this because you got to think that
that number two person thinks they're
going to propose to you and and I've
been to the final three so you start
thinking about what its gonna be like to
meet the family and you start writing
out like what you would say and they
have you do that before and then you
know I gotta go in here and break this
person's heart yeah I was writing vows
you know what I was gonna say in my
proposal speech and everything I would
say the two days before I was actually
for the first time nervous but then the
day of the proposal I had complete
clarity and it's like look if she does
not choose me then it is what it is she
wasn't the one for me there we go but I
had given it all my all so I was really
confident in that yeah you got to
realize the other person the number 2
person thinks I'm gonna spend the rest
of my life with this person and you know
no you're not remember watching and and
it was so dramatic because I could
relate a lot to you and the number 2
person because there it was very fraught
like there's a lot of conflict saying
number 2 let's just call him it
seemed like there was this like this
drama that like he was very conflicted
and sort of wishy-washy with all due
respect but like I related to dating
guys like that so like I really want to
be with you and yet I can forgot what
his issues were but he had a lot of
issues commitment issues yeah and that's
why I wanted to I didn't want my final
proposal to be muddied with oh I had to
send this person home and then 10
minutes later I'm gonna accept the you
know proposal from the person and spend
the rest of my life with I was very
Ataman I totally long I was like I want
to send the number two person home the
night before and I hate how it played
out on TV because I was very
matter-of-fact about that but it it was
still hard you know it doesn't matter
when you do it it's tough that's gonna
be the hardest you're right thinks
they're though they think they won I
remember I was like was the beginning
season yeah it was raining I remember
that it was it was and you sent him home
right yeah I've like walked out and
everything my sister now oh my god it
was super emotional but I remember when
I started the season I was like if I
find somebody I'm gonna have no problem
sending these people at home I'm
ruthless when it comes to this like I'm
an attorney
false attorney it's black and white
that's the law this is gray and hard and
it's tough and just imagine somebody is
cleaning they're just like no stay with
me I want to be with you we can work it
out you're like I don't know if you want
to do it okay how would you people go I
don't know I would be oh my god they
hurt me oh man I couldn't wait to say
like that would be fun to do but um just
listening to this season don't you want
to watch this season go back and watch
and now you know that it works out you
know how it ends there's a happy ending
they got married two years later this is
a real show that really actually worked
for Rachel Lindsay and and Brian
Ebersole oh thank you so much for being
here watch it on to be now you can watch
the whole season season 13 of The
Bachelorette correct yes lucky season 13
on to B now stream it as soon as you can
tomorrow is when is is literally as soon
as you can thanks so much for being here
you guys
you were so fun and I loved your season
definitely watch it guys you gotta go on
dates good job of this we check in in a
month you go on at least three days it's
three first dates with one of these
right guys with three days right guys
okay and then after you experiment with
it and you actually do it rather than
these ideas and these stories I just
think Riya is letting
a lot of riff oh I just got a direct
message from who a direct requests on
Raya let's see that's weird that that
just came in mmm what's wrong with him
so he paid $1.99 to send that to me
the guy's got money paid an extra dollar
too much I feel like you're the girl
that like when like you're you pretty
got a good personality like you're the
girl though that like when the guys like
I'm tired of perfect models that
are vapid and don't and don't really
feel my you know my brain cuz I'm so
smart and interesting myself I need
something like that and in your day they
called me and I hooked them up with my
friend Sarah Lina yeah yeah yeah or then
they date you and then you tell them
everything that's actually wrong with
them that they don't ever have never
been told before cuz no one's honest
with them and then they're like let's go
back to vapid yeah yeah yeah I
challenge them you mean yeah mm-hmm
challenges can be pretty pretty annoying
you want to talk about that no
[Music]
you have anything going on in Rio right
now um yeah you can check out my Raya
this is always fun oh yeah there's some
there's some things you're gonna be
disappointed in me for some of this
stuff he's 39
well he's gets injections on his face
looks like Ben Affleck there yeah how's
he rain you know this let's go to guys
that right you how are you okay haha yes
I suppose that feels good to hear I am
good headed to Florida for shows now you
sound soupy soupy looks super What did
he say sounds sounds soupy I didn't even
see that that would have been that yeah
but that would have been the end I
didn't see soupy sounds soupy I'm well
giving blood now but I'm headed to New
Orleans on Sunday actually alright
here's Josh he's 30 lives in New York
from Los Angeles he works he works in
the business Josh so he's an agent of
some sort I don't know I guess I don't
know I don't know what that company is
can I say the name it no okay okay I
don't even know what it was or debating
or whether or not to tell you that I've
seen you do stand-up and I think you're
10 out of 10 funny cuz you didn't
write back did he write yeah I want
to know the time difference of when he
wrote so right away you don't like
this you don't like a compliment you
don't want him to seem like a fan you
want to seem like he's on your level so
desirey turns you off it it wasn't that
it was I think sometimes when you're
swiping you just like are not as
discerning as you would be at other
times like there are certain days of my
period where I'm like I like anyone or
and then there are other days where I'm
like I won't take anyone like there my
tastes change so I think I matched with
this guy and then the next day start
writing me and I looked again at him and
I thought I tried to Tim you didn't
write back and then you wrote back three
days later
what's that right you wrote that's
really nice thank you you're handsome oh
yeah my friend made me write that my
friend made me
that okay I did not want to say that but
then someone was like just be nice he
gave you a compliment say you're
handsome see what happens so then you
write he doesn't write back two days
later he write or no you write
and I like calling back yes and then he
writes great call back and he roads in
does parenthesis did I do that right
which you hate I know you hate anyone
would like the comedies
still blushing honestly so watching I
know God is drying yeah you know what I
think it was is because he complimented
that I was 10 out of 10 funny and I'm
like yeah I know why don't you tell me
I'm pretty
and so that's why I complimented his
look so as to nudge him to be like yeah
do you want to put your dick in me and
any right and then he weren't another
comedy thing so what now do we small
talk
what's metric do you only listen to
music without lyrics do I make a joke
about st. Louis that slightly offends
you
I kind of liked that that cuz that
happens so often well you didn't like it
enough to write him back cuz then it was
the next day and he wrote and then
14 days later he rose again oh here
we go Jason you wrote back to Jason okay
July 14th
let's see what Jason knows Jason
designer cool creative 38 good age
unsure lives in New York
hey there fellow Midwestern er it's nice
opening hey there you wrote way back hey
there do you get told all the time that
you're nice too then he writes back
three days later at least ten times a
day I say off and people laugh and
say oh you're so nice funny hmm cute and
then he writes you literally almost some
june/july on a monthly I had figure out
a month a month later he writes is that
too harsh and you never wrote
this head back why because I don't want
to get to know these gentlemen they're
not gonna make the cut
they I'm too picky I'm only gonna
disappoint that I'm gonna go out on a
date with them they're gonna get all
dressed up they're gonna put a lot of
effort into it they're gonna think maybe
that they're gonna get AB sighs you are
overthinking it I'm going to disappoint
them and it's just like I'd rather not
even just do it
he's got me and Julio down by the
schoolyard don't put so much on it don't
care so you go out on a date for
30 minutes there doesn't need to be like
this huge connection are worried about
them how do you know right these people
back what do you mean they're all solid
candidates any girl would die to have
these guys they'll be writing them
really yeah okay well you got to put
yourself out there you gotta at least go
on the date mmm how about this you go on
a date after you're done with your
Netflix special I have so many of these
people Jesus yeah well the guy that I
went on so how can we still feel neg I
know how you can't I still do it too
like when I would guys I actually like
don't want to date me these guys are
better than the guys you actually like I
know that's the problem they're actually
available hey guys you just watch the
clip for my radio show you up with Nikki
Glaser that you can hear every morning
on Comedy Central radio sirius XM
channel 95 10:00 to 12:00 Eastern and
you can check out a clip here on YouTube
every Tuesday or check out my podcast No